// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is a genre of speculative fiction dealing with imaginative concepts such as futuristic science and technology, space travel, time travel, faster than light travel, a parallel universe, and extraterrestrial life.",
    answer: "c. Science Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Science Fiction",
      "d. Creative Non-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "A literary genre that combines three media: book, movie/video, and internet website.",
    answer: "a. Digi-Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "A literary presentation where the author incorporates doodle writing and drawings and handwritten graphics in place of the traditional font.",
    answer: "b. Doodle Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Science Fiction",
      "d. Creative Non-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Stories told almost entirely in dialogue, simulating social network exchanges.",
    answer: "d. Text-Talk Novel",
    options: [
      "a. Chick Lit",
      "b. Digi-Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Text-Talk Novel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "It is a genre fiction that addresses issues of modern womanhood, often humorously and lightheartedly.",
    answer: "a. Chick Lit",
    options: [
      "a. Chick Lit",
      "b. Digi-Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Text-Talk Novel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "It is a website that contains short articles posted and changed regularly.",
    answer: "a. Blog",
    options: [
      "a. Blog",
      "b. Flash Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Digi-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Digital literature that uses links and includes parts that move or mutate.",
    answer: "d. Digi-Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Blog",
      "b. Flash Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Digi-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It is a comic book or book series published in Japan.",
    answer: "d. Manga",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Illustrated Novel",
      "d. Manga"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Stories characterized by their brevity. It could range from a word to a thousand.",
    answer: "b. Flash Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Creative Nonfiction",
      "b. Flash Fiction",
      "c. Blog",
      "d. Hyper Poetry"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Narrative work in which a story is told using a comic form.",
    answer: "c. Graphic Novel",
    options: [
      "a. Manga",
      "b. Digi-Fiction",
      "c. Graphic Novel",
      "d. Illustrated Novel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "39 Clues book series by Scholastic, where stories are told using the combination of book, video, and website, is an example of this literary genre.",
    answer: "a. Digi-Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Science Fiction",
      "d. Creative Non-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Mashable by Pete Cashmore, where feature stories around the world are posted and updated, is an example of this literary genre.",
    answer: "a. Blog",
    options: [
      "a. Blog",
      "b. Flash Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Digi-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "A story that develops through a screenshot of SMS conversation like Vince and Kath by Jenny Ruth Almocera is an example of this literary genre.",
    answer: "d. Text-Talk Novel",
    options: [
      "a. Chick Lit",
      "b. Digi-Fiction",
      "c. Hyper Poetry",
      "d. Text-Talk Novel"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "A story that uses literary techniques to create accurate narratives like travel and nature stories in Robert Macfarlaneâ€™s The Wild Places is an example of this literary genre.",
    answer: "d. Creative Non-Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Science Fiction",
      "d. Creative Non-Fiction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "The Hunger Games series that explores dystopian or post-apocalyptic themes is an example of this literary genre.",
    answer: "a. Digi-Fiction",
    options: [
      "a. Digi-Fiction",
      "b. Doodle Fiction",
      "c. Science Fiction",
      "d. Creative Non-Fiction"
    ]
  }
];
